hi guys uh welcome to this
short presentation about a game-changing
opportunity
in the life insurance industry this is a
game changing because
this is something that you have never
seen before
in any company and in fact this
new developments with fwd and life
insurance industry is brought about
by the crisis and
kovit19 so we had to adapt to
the changing climate and the changing
times if the
fwd affiliate is a way of doing business
in the life insurance industry without
having to take an exam
without registering for a license but
hopefully
all of you who decide to join fwd
affiliate
will eventually join us in our sales
team
and you can and some of you who who even
wants to
join us in this business but don't have
the resources to pay for the exams which
will cost about 2000 pesos
and for the license which will cost
about another two thousand for total
five thousand pesos
if it some of the affiliates who don't
have the funds yet to take these exams
and the license
and the licensing requirements you may
use whatever money you earn from being
an affiliate
to have that opportunity to be
a planner as well or you can just also
uh remain an affiliate and earn from
this because
the business is very simple it's just
sharing even even sharing your links
will already
earn you money alright so let me proceed
with fwd affiliate
so this program was
created to answer a few questions number
one
is we ask the agents the planners ask
who we can talk about fwd
which family do i see to help prepare
for
any financial setbacks and how we can
utilize the digital tools that
fwd has prepared for us and how we can
maximize the remote selling
opportunities
that are that is available only now
because previously when you offer life
insurance products you have to offer
this
face to face in person but now we can
already offer the business
through remote selling and fwd affiliate
is really a great addition to our
business
so we have a mission
to share protect and earn
so i'd like to to encourage you while
listening to this presentation i'd like
to encourage you to download the app you
can download
it at the play store or app store
and before you do so you register
as an affiliate you can do it right now
immediately it's very fast it will take
less than a minute if you are watching
this
from youtube there is a link below this
video if you are watching this from a
blog or
or from a landing page there is a link
somewhere where you can go
just register your name your email
address and you are set to go and then
you log into your account to your app
it's
just very fast it's very easy to do this
business
so fwd affiliates lets you generate more
leads
through the app because you can you can
con the app is connected
directly to your other communication
apps as well through messenger
facebook viper and you can see inside
your app
what other communication channels you
can
communicate directly with your contacts
it will increase your online and social
media presence especially because fwd
already prepared
a lot of content inside the app which
you can share immediately
it's right at its business right at your
fingertips
you can also recruit affiliates straight
from your app and the link is already
there inside your app whether you are an
affiliate or a planner you can
continuously recruit affiliates
and earn from the activities of your of
your affiliates
and fwd affiliates makes it easy
for you to increase your sales
especially if you are already
a planner because all affiliates under
you
all their sales will be credited to you
all right so when we say share protect
and earn let me
break it down to all of you now we share
because
it will be very easy for us to spread
awareness about
our products about opportunities we will
be sharing financial literacy
to people especially when you share
content that is prepared by fwd
and is already at your fingertips you
will be able to share what we can do for
others
our mission investments and products
now when we say our mission we we
what i want to emphasize that our
business is built
on our uh mission to
to educate filipino people
because it's uh there is a survey that
says only
less than 10 of the filipinos are
adequately insured
they don't have enough savings to last
them through
crisis so this is a good opportunity for
us to educate
filipinos protect
because we will be offering protection
plans
with fwd affiliates we will be
offering our cando plans which is a khan
men
can live can guard which are
different kinds of products and awesome
products which are very
affordable at only 1 800 pesos per year
we also have our regular policies that
digital products like
set for health and the digital set for
tomorrow it's a health insurance
and a term insurance these are great
products and the details
you can find the details actually in our
online shop
now we earn how do we earn we are the
agents can earn commissions
quarterly volume bonuses and other
bonuses not only from their own sales
but from the sales of all affiliates
under you
now if if you're an agent and you are
able to to invite an affiliate and the
affiliate also recruits other affiliates
all those affiliates under you will all
be credited
to you all right so you will not earn
the same commission
as if it was your own sales but
it's it's it's a bonus because you don't
anymore sell those products and you
still earn the commissions for
affiliates
you will be earning rewards which is
equivalent to cash because you will be
receiving sodexo passes
based on your activity from sharing
to inviting affiliates and also to
selling
so i'd like to remind you if you have
already downloaded your app because it
will be
much it will be easier to navigate if i
discuss this while you have your
app in front of you but
this is really a very simple tool it
will not be difficult for you to
to do this to explore the app on your
own even without
this this uh lecture
and so this is how it appears to this is
how the app appears to a financial
advisors now you wish
you will have your own photo there you
can upload your own photo
you can have a brief description about
yourself
right so this will show up every time
you
send an affiliate link
so yes these are uh some of the
things that because the the interface of
this app will be different for
for planners and it will also be
different for
affiliates who are not planners
so when uh when a prospect will tap on
your photo
inside the app it will will display
that the description that you wrote
yourself
you can also call your leads straight
from the affiliate from the
affiliate app in case you want to to
talk to them to encourage them or to
offer them other products it's very easy
to
to contact them right inside your
dashboard because all your recruits will
be there inside your dashboard
all right so i will discuss with you uh
how you can earn so
our target market here is really wide
because of the simplicity of this
of this system this business you can go
working moms even moms who are stay at
home
millennials professionals ofw's
businessmen your friends everyone this
discovers the whole gamut
everyone because uh you don't need to
take an exam you didn't you don't need
any any licensing you don't even need
experience and
you just send out your your
messages your links to your friends i'm
sure you have
thousands of people on your cell phone
on your in your
through your through your contacts to
your facebook friends
instagram followers the list is
endless you don't have to spam all of
them you can send to
to 10 people to 20 people every day
and follow up to them like the following
week
so uh the opportunity is really here for
you
and so we share with purpose because
we add value to other people and we
reconnect with them
and we build connections with them
because
we have to to have that mindset that
when we share these products
we are actually helping these people we
are protecting
their investments protecting their
future and securing their financial
future now we add value by
sharing relevant content to tailored to
individuals when you when you
look at your app and see the if you see
all those content from fwd you can share
specific content
to some of your contacts who might be
where if you feel like this content is
relevant to that particular contact
then you share that to them and you add
your own words as well
and it's also a good way to build a
connection with your friends especially
some of them you have you have not
connected with for a long time but you
don't have to sell to them immediately
you don't have to to to sound so
salesy but you but if you have a mindset
that your product
is helping other people then i think it
would not be difficult for you to share
these things
to your friends now you can also send
your own personal url of products in the
fwd shop this
is relevant especially to agents because
the links in your app are already tied
to your personal url
and it's automatically all sales from
that
url from that link will automatically be
credited to you
so if i prospect will click on those
links this
is how it will look like on their mobile
phones
we only show mobile phones here because
i think about ninety percent of
purchases of ninety percent of online
activities are now on mobile
so this is how it looks like the
customer now every time
when when they decide to buy from this
you automatically get
credit i will discuss later how much you
can earn
as affiliates all right so this is what
i
talked about if there when you look look
at your app and you
look down on your the lower portion of
your phone
the middle part is a share button when
you click it you will have
two options and thus those two options
are are shown on top at the top portion
of your screen
there there is a an option for fwd posts
these are contents
from fwd and if you see that button that
says copy link and share
that that button already contains your
affiliate link
okay and any activity from that link
will be credited to you and there is
also the other tab which is your own
post
it's if you want to share your own
affiliate link
to go into the online shop the fwd
online shop so if your
friend your customer will click on that
share link
they will be directed to the fwd shop
and all purchases will automatically be
credited to you
so if you're a planner all the all the
purchases from all affiliates under you
the sale will be credited to you
as far as the points as far as the
commissions
are concerned now the points will go
to the affiliate okay planners don't
earn
any affiliate points
so if we want to maximize
this system we have to it would be we
highly suggested that we recruit
affiliates actively
especially it's very easy because it's
very fast it will take less than a
minute to
to to register and to download maybe
about another minute to download
and it costs nothing and in fact you can
earn even just by sharing content
so we can actively recruit by
communicating
our mission as planners as affiliates
for a very
awesome industry
we can share it to our target prospect
with basically everyone who knows how to
handle a smartphone
and it is also important that we recruit
the right affiliates especially
if you intend to become an insurance
leader
in the next few months
so we communicate our mission
by telling them in in
in a proper context how it depends on
our relationship with that person we
tell them that we are in the business of
securing lives of many filipinos
tell them that our products will
mitigate
uncertainties setbacks this is really
a very noble business can you imagine
if right now you are able to offer a
health insurance product
to a friend and then
you forget about it and after 10 years
that friend
meets an accident or a medical emergency
and he was able to have himself
cured because you offered him
a medical product a health product 10
years before
wouldn't it feel great that this is
really a very
noble business you you earn by helping
other people protect their financial
future we actively recruit affiliates by
sharing this to our target prospects
prospects
who are entrepreneurial
prospects who are centers of influence
prospects who have a lot of contacts i
mean
the the list is really unless we if if
only for affiliates we don't really have
to choose so much because
there is no quota there is there are no
fees you don't have to look for someone
who can afford an exam or
a registration because there is none we
just need someone who has a smartphone
and has an internet connection
so we can share awareness very
easily because fwd already provides us
articles and content which we can find
in our app
and i we also have our own group i
created we
have a facebook group and then i will be
sharing with you a lot of
of material which you can use to share
so that we will not be limited
only by fwd graphics but some
we can also alternate it with other
graphics that don't sell because we
don't want to be selling
every day on our facebook maybe we can
just sell every once in a while
send messages but we should we also need
to send
messages send graphics that do not sell
it
it me it will be very spammy and you
will be blocked if you conti if you
if you just share anything that is about
selling or because people do in general
people want to buy but they do not want
to be sold to
so gustanilang bentahan so we don't want
to make them feel that we are just there
to sell
and sell and sell
okay so how do you start you just start
by registering as an affiliate and then
earn
rewards rewards so your friends can join
afterwards after you register as an
affiliate
so what is required is that you just
need to be a legal resident
of the philippines at least 18 years old
at the time of registration you should
be duly registered as an affiliate for
authorized channels so as i mentioned if
you see any link below this
it is very it will be very clear
wherever you are watching this whether
from youtube from facebook
or from a blog okay there's a link there
it's an authorized link
and you must have not been
convicted of a crime must not be an
active fwd insurance distributor because
fwd agents cannot be affiliates but
you can recruit affiliates and you must
not have
a previous registration in the program
under
any email address or alias so you can
only have one affiliate
account
all right so how do we earn
what are the rewards of this uh smart
affiliate program
fwd affiliate program here are
the rewards
so if you have a thousand points you can
convert it to a hundred pesos sodexo
pass
you can redeem it online 3 000 points is
300 peso
6000 points is 600 pesos
so how do you earn points you earn one
point for every
sharing activity if you share your links
from your app
if you share it to facebook to your
friends
as long as you you do it directly from
the app because
there is a tracker from your app and the
fwd system
will will find out will be able to
compute that you are sharing
your link so you get one point and with
a limit of 50 points per day
you will also get points if one of your
leads will sign up as an affiliate
so a limit of 500 points per day you can
recruit 10 affiliates every day
okay take note affiliates can also
recruit other affiliates
you get 10 50 points for every affiliate
sign up
now you also have 400 points for every
sale of a can do product
okay the affiliate learn 400
points from a sale of a kandu product
so uh these products there there will be
a different discussion about this but
you can see this
on on the fwd website you search for can
do
and then for the two other digi for the
two other policies is set for tomorrow
which is a term insurance
there's also uh set for health
it's 6 000 points for the affiliate okay
so we can show you sample computation of
what you will earn for us how much you
can earn for a set of activities
all right so knowledge check how many
points will
an affiliate earn when he shares a
content it's one point
when the lead signs up it's 50 points
when the lead purchases a con man
product
400 points affiliate
invites leads it's 50 points yes
and then uh buys set for health it's 6
but if an affiliate buys a policy for
himself doesn't earn anything
and then here is an example right an
illustration let's
let's uh look at an
affiliate cindy now say for example this
is her activity for one week
he shared she shared 50 contents
50 articles whole week like that's seven
shares every day she gets 50 points that
week
she has 20 leads signed up to the 20
leads times 50 points that's a thousand
points
now two leads converted also purchased
it's 12 000 points for the policies okay
these are this this is either set for
health or set for tomorrow so it's
twelve thousand points because it's six
thousand points each
now the lead purchases five can do
products so
it's either can bend can help can guard
it's 400 each so it's 2 000 points so
she gets a total of
15 050 fwd
points which the 15 thousand is worth
one five already so dex will give
certificates which you can use in a lot
of establishments
includes sm so this is just equivalent
to cash actually
so do planners earn fwd points uh
planners will earn the commissions set
up
uh at uh 70 percent of this usual
commission on each product
right so
now how much will an affiliate earn if
he or she recruits another affiliate she
earns 100 points
for every sale of his
affiliate recruit okay never mind i will
i will show you an illustration later to
make this easier to understand
and for every policy the affiliate
recruiter
will get one five points for every sale
that's that his recruit
can make the recruiter can also get
a thousand five hundred points
so you can only earn up to your directly
invited affiliates like if example
uh i invite i'm an affiliate and i
invite another affiliate i will earn
from his
sale but if that affiliate also invites
another affiliate i won't be
able to earn any more from that sale
because it will be
that recruit who will earn from that act
from those activities
all right so
a recruited affiliates lead buys set for
tomorrow
the lead will earn six thousand points
the recruiter will earn one five
so to illustrate let's go back to our
original
example of cindy and then cindy was able
to invite jeff now jeff was able to sell
one con man
and he also bought set for
life all right so 6 000 fwd points
and 400 fwd points for this product so
jeff gets
6400 well cindy
earns 1 600 out of the activity
of jeff right so the more you recruit
the more you invite is the more you earn
it cost
totally nothing so i don't see any
reason why we don't share
why we don't recruit because even just
by sharing a loan we already earn
so we have every reason to share plus we
are adding value to the life
of our prospects now here is another
example
jeff invites tammy so jeff will be
earning from
tami's activities but cindy will no
longer earn from tommy
but if you are a financial planner
who recruited cindy yeah you
earn your commissions from the sales of
cindy jeff and tommy now you earn 70
percent of the regular commission of how
much you were supposed to earn if you
were the one
if you were the one who sold that
product all right
now for the information of the
affiliates listening here the usual
commission is around 30 to 50
of a product for example that
that's set for health if if uh if the
agent is supposed to earn 40
and you are able to sell a 30 000 annual
a product with a 30 000 annual premium
the agent will earn
around maybe twelve thousand depends on
the pay may period
maybe let's just say ten thousand now
because if if the agent was the one who
or the planner was the one who sold the
product he would have earned ten
thousand
but because it was the affiliate who
earned who who sold it the affiliate
earned 66 000 points
the recruiter earns a thousand five
hundred points and the agent earned
seven thousand
pesos so for the affiliates this will
really be
great stepping stone for you to earn
more to see it is this will make you
have a taste of a life of a financial
planner
now aside from the opportunities the
rewards you get
this is also another opportunity for you
to help other people
by sharing this opportunity and also to
help other people
by giving them products that will help
secure
their families and not only that
it could be a good opportunity for you
to explore a career in the insurance
industry
you can invite other affiliates or you
can join fwd
as a planner so
in summary by joining our fwd affiliate
program you get to earn
fwd points you get the ability
to help other people by inviting them
and by
offering them our products and also you
get a chance to explore
wonderful career and the possibilities
that you can have
as a financial wealth planner
with fud all right so
this ends my presentation about the
affiliate program of fwd and so
let us encourage all of you to join
share with purpose recruit actively
and get be rewarded with and will be
rewarded with
all these opportunities so all you need
to do is click the link
below or above or wherever you see it
click the link to join
download the app and then you will see
a link to contact us so we may proceed
with
your questions if you have other
inquiries and that's all
and i hope to see you really soon